<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Girl\'s flu</string>
    <string name="remedie">During menstruation, the muscles of the uterus contract(tighten) to help the body remove the lining of the endometrium.
    this can be quite uncomfartable for certain women. This type of discomfort is called menstrual pains. Menstrual pains can be relieved by light exercise,
        a warm bath, or a pad that produces heat. Theere are certain medications that can relieve pain, but it is best to consult with the doctor.</string>
    <string name="r">Some women have very painful periods that can force them to stay in bed for a couple of days in each cycle.</string>
    <string name="ra">7 Home remedies to relieve menstrual cramps</string>

    <string name="le">An excellent homemade solution for menstrual cramps is the poultice of lavender, because this medicinal plant is stimulant of the peripheral circulation.</string>
    <string name="li">50g of lavender leaves;\n1 Litre of water</string>
    <string name="lp">Place the lavender leaves in the water and let boil. After allowing to cool, remove the leaves and apply them on the abdomen 2 to 3 times a day.</string>

    <string name="me">The tea leaves mango has antispasmodic properties being useful to ease colic.</string>
    <string name="mi">20g of mango leaves;\n
1 liter of boiling water.
</string>
    <string name="mp">Place the ingredients in a pot and boil for 5 minutes. Cover and cool a little, then strain and sweeten with 1 teaspoon of honey, per cup. However,
        this should be added only when the tea is going to be drunk, and not in the whole liter of tea.

        \n\nFor colic to be less intense in a natural way, this tea should be taken 4 times a day, in the two days before the menstruation fall and during the first day
            of menstruation.
</string>

    <string name="ae">The tea of agnus castus or chasteberry has sedative and antispasmodic properties that help to balance the hormonal levels, being effective not only in relieving
    colic, but also other symptoms related to menstruation such as pimples, PMS and irregularities of the menstrual cycle. </string>

    <string name="ai">1 tablespoon of agnus castus;
        \n200 ml of boiling water
</string>
    <string name="ap">Add the ingredients in a pot and let stand for about 15 minutes. Then you should strain and drink 2 to 4 times a day.

        \n\nCare should be taken when administering tea doses, since high doses can cause intestinal problems.
</string>

    <string name="bi">1 tablespoon of basil;\n500 ml of boiling water

</string>
    <string name="bp">Place the ingredients in a pot and boil for a few minutes. Let cool and drink then. You should drink this re for every 6 hours, without sugar, because sugar can worsen menstrual cramps.
</string>

    <string name="mue">A good home remedy to end colic is Artemisia tea, because it has antispasmodic action that reduces pain and abdominal discomfort, caused by intestinal or menstrual cramps.</string>
    <string name="mui">1 tablespoon of mugwort leaves;
        \n1 cup of boiling water

</string>

    <string name="mup">Add the ingredients and let stand for about 5 minutes. Then cover, let cool, strain and drink 2 to 3 cups a day.

        \n\nTo increase the effect of this tea, the woman can place a bag of warm water on the belly and lie on her side.
</string>

    <string name="ge">A good natural solution for menstrual cramps is ginger tea with chamomile. This tea is an effective mixture, because while ginger acts as anti-inflammatory reducing pains,
        chamomile acts as an tranquilizer providing the necessary relaxation during this period of the month.
</string>
    <string name="gi">1 tablespoon of chopped ginger;
        \n1 tablespoon of dried chamomile;
        \n500 ml of water
</string>
    <string name="gp">The ginger root should be boiled in a covered container for about 5 minutes, after the solution is removed from the fire add chamomile.
        The container should be capped again and remain infused for 10 minutes. \nAfter being strained and sweetened with honey, the tea is ready to drink. Drinking 3 cups a day is
        enough to decrease menstrual cramps. </string>

    <string name="ce">The Calendula tea with anise and nutmeg, because they contain several antispasmodic, analgesic, anti-inflammatory and soothing properties that are beneficial to
        regulate menstruation.
</string>
    <string name="ci">1 handful of Calendula flowers;
        \n1 tablespoon nutmeg;
        \n tablespoon of anise;
        \n1 glass of water
</string>
    <string name="cp">Place the ingredients in a pot and boil for 10 minutes. Then turn off the heat, cover the pot and let cool. Next you should strain, sweeten to taste, and drink
        twice a day.
</string>

    <string name="precautions1">It is important to educate the girl about what menstruation consists of, since otherwise it can be a major shock when it occurs for the first time,
        not understanding the origin of the blood or the changes that your body suffers. In the same way, it is advisable to educate about the care that menstruation requires, since it
        is something that you will have to live with during a large part of your life. Thus, it must be explained not only why it is produced, but also the use of compresses, for example,
        and the necessary hygiene habits.
\n\nIn addition, since the menarche the woman is already considered fertile and capable of reproducing, so it is also important to offer guidance on issues such as sexuality or
    contraceptive methods.</string>

    <string name="precaution2">The onset of menarche is part of a "girl's" puberty and, beyond presenting the first menstruation and beginning her fertile period, it also implies a series of changes throughout the body, such as the following:
</string>

    <string name="precaution3">You may be transitioning into menopause if you begin experiencing some or all of the following symptoms:
</string>

    <string name="ec1">1.You’re breaking out Acne is a common problem at this time of the month. Adult women get acne much more than men do, and it’s all because of hormones.
        Period-related breakouts are called cyclical acne. Rising hormone levels kickstart oil (called sebum) production, which clogs pores and causes pimples as your period is
        about to start. Before or during your period, you may notice breakouts on your chin and jawline area.\n\n

2.   Your breasts are sore or heavy.Breast pain linked to periods is called cyclical breast pain. Your breasts may feel tender or swollen right after ovulation until a few days
            after period bleeding starts. Changes in the hormones estrogen, progesterone, and prolactin, the breastfeeding hormone, may play a role.\n\n
3.You’re tired but you can’t sleep. Fatigue is a vicious cycle for many women at this point in their cycle. Shifting hormones disturb your sleep patterns and make you feel tired.
        Changes in estrogen and progesterone may also increase core body temperature, especially when sleeping. You’re more likely to get good sleep when your core body temperature
        decreases.\n\n
                4.You have cramps. Cramps in your lower belly are the most frequent menstrual complaint. Cramps that occur before or during your period are called primary dysmenorrhea. Unlike many
        other symptoms, which begin 1-2 weeks before your period and end when bleeding starts, cramps usually show up right before your period and last for 2-3 days.\n\n
5.You’re constipated or have diarrhea. When your period is coming, digestive symptoms tend to fall to the extremes. Some women get constipated. Others have diarrhea.\n\n
6.You’re bloated and gassy. Water retention is another major complaint. It’s also hormonal, but you can curb premenstrual bloat by cutting out salt, eating more fruits and vegetables,
        and exercising regularly.\n\n

7.You have a headache. Changes in estrogen levels are to blame if you get headaches before your period. If you’re prone to migraines, you’ll probably find that you get them before
        your period.\n\n

8 .You’re having mood swings. The shift in hormones that cause physical period signs can also affect your emotions. You may have crying spells or feel angry and irritable.\n\n
9.You’re anxious and depressed. Depression and anxiety are commonly linked to PMS. About half the women who seek help for period signs have some type of depression or anxiety disorder.
        A history of either condition could make your premenstrual symptoms worse.\n\n

10.Your lower back hurts. Period cramps don’t just affect the belly. Changes in natural chemicals called prostaglandins that line the uterus cause contractions that you could also
        feel in your back or thighs.
</string>

    <string name="ec2">1.Hot flashes (a sudden feeling of warmth that spreads over the body).\n\n
2.Night sweats and/or cold flashes.\n\n
3.Vaginal dryness; discomfort during sex.\n\n
4.Urinary urgency (a pressing need to urinate more frequently).\n\n
5.Difficulty sleeping (insomnia).\n\n
6.Emotional changes (irritability, mood swings, mild depression).\n\n
7.Dry skin, dry eyes or dry mouth.\n\n

        People who are still in the menopause transition (perimenopause) may also experience:\n\n

1.Breast tenderness.\n
2.Worsening of premenstrual syndrome (PMS).\n
3.Irregular periods or skipping periods.\n
4.Periods that are heavier or lighter than usual.\n\n
        Some people might also experience:\n\n
6.Racing heart.\n
7.Headaches.\n
8.Joint and muscle aches and pains.\n
9.Changes in libido (sex drive).\n
10.Difficulty concentrating, memory lapses (often temporary).\n
11.Weight gain.\n
12.Hair loss or thinning.
</string>


    <string name="myth1">f you start to hear that your friends have already arrived, you may feel that something is wrong with you. The reality is that the body of each girl is totally different and the same applies in the case of menstruation.
The first menstruation, called menarche, takes place between 8 and 15 years. However, if this does not happen it is considered primary amenorrhea (absence of menstruation), and it is important to consult a gynecologist.
    </string>

    <string name="myth2">If you practice any physical activity or go to the gym every day, your period is not an impediment, just the opposite! With exercise your body produces endorphins, also called happiness hormones, which act as a natural analgesic in your body and help improve your mood.
    Although if you want to rest, it is also valid, you can even do something lighter, such as taking a short walk.</string>

    <string name="myth3">With regard to performing water activities during those days, there are many versions, but one of the most common is that the period is cut off when in contact with water. However, the period is a process that is not controlled by external factors, but by the detachment of the endometrium as a result of hormonal discharge.
Some girls may have the feeling that the period is interrupted, because they are upright or because of the water pressure, however, the flow does not stop and, although the water as such does not represent any danger to your health, it is Its important that you make sure you use the right protection.
    </string>

    <string name="myth4">

Unless you tell them, there is no way for anyone to know that you are in your period. While you may have some symptoms such as acne or swelling, these are only noticeable to you.
In addition, it is important that you affirm that your period is something completely natural and that the most important thing is that you choose what makes you feel comfortable. For example, if you are worried about someone noticing your towel, you can try ultra-thin towels or tampons.
</string>

    <string name="myth5">
Buffers have many advantages, such as staying protected when practicing your favorite sport or swimming in family vacations, but they are an option that still causes many doubts or fears. One of them is that only the biggest girls can use them or they can make them lose their virginity.
Virginity is often associated with the hymen, a very thin and elastic membrane that has perforations in the center in order to allow passage of the flow during the period, but these openings are large enough to insert a tampon. Although it is true that it can break even after a fall, for practicing some sport or for a very abundant menstrual flow.
</string>

    <string name="myth6">
When girls share their experiences with their friends or partners, they tend to compare and can create wrong ideas of what is "normal". In the case of the duration of your period, this can be between 3 and 7 days long, that is, as long as you are in this range you have nothing to worry about.
You should also consider that during the 2 years after your first period you can detect some irregularities, because your hormonal system is not yet fully mature.
</string>

    <string name="myth7">
Another of the most popular beliefs among girls is that for a period to be regular it must arrive on the same date each month. The truth is that each girl has an individual pattern of behavior in regard to their periods. As long as your periods arrive every 21 to 35 days there is nothing to worry about.
Many times what is considered irregular is really only a lack of knowledge about how your menstrual cycles work in particular, so it is advisable to make a record of each one so that you understand how your body works.
</string>

    <string name="myth8">
Although the probability is less, you can continue to ovulate during the days of your period, as well as being more prone to contract sexually transmitted infections. That is why it is advisable that if you have sex during this time, use a barrier method of contraception (condom).
</string>

    <string name="myth9">
If you have symptoms such as fatigue, mood swings or trouble sleeping, they are not in your head! They can be part of Premenstrual Syndrome, a set of symptoms that appear (from 3 to 10 days) before the period, as a consequence of the symptoms. hormonal changes.
It is important that within the record of your period, you also include these discomforts and their intensity.
</string>

    <string name="myth10"><b>
10) </b>There is food that hurts you during your period There is no food or drink that represents a danger to your health if you take it during your period, it is only advisable that you eat healthy and stay hydrated.</string>

    <string name="recommendations"><b>Recommendations to help your daughter with her first rule. If your mom has not done it yet, tell her to explain each of these recommendations</b>

        \n\n1. First of all, before that moment arrives, inform him of what it is, why, and the consequences that it has, so that it is not a shock and he is scared. It is time to talk lightly about sexuality, since from that moment comes the fertile age, without too much emphasis if the girl is very small because it will be the last thing she wants to hear now.\n\n
2. Congratulate the girl, as she now knows that she has a normal maturation of the body and reproductive capacity.\n\n
3. Avoid transmitting the negative effects, much less the antiquated myths.\n\n
4. Teach her how to use tampons, compresses or menstrual cup. It is not true that intimate hygiene measures that are introduced into the body can not be used from the first rule. The tampons or the menstrual cup will make you pass your rule without hardly knowing and with a more normalized lifestyle.\n\n
5. Do all the activities you were doing normally, if your abdomen does not hurt.\n\n
6. Hygiene should be extreme during those days. Teach her how.\n\n
7. Give her a calendar so that she can write down the days of the rule and what they last, since during the first two years they can be a little chaotic until they finish regularizing.\n\n
8. It is recommended that the father be involved and participate in this event with total naturalness, serving as support for the mother.\n\n
9. Tell your experience so you do not feel alone and know that we have all had to go through that. Let her get angry, feel proud or shut up in her room to think, she will need to express her emotions and you should not get angry or worry about it.\n\n
10. Recommend that from now on always carry a tampon or a compress in your school bag, since the irregularity can make you pass bad passes.</string>

    <string name="yoga1">There are some people who rock their Lululemon’s and actually go to yoga. And there are other people who are sporting yoga pants and laying in savasana...in
        their bed while they watch Netflix. Hey, no judgment. But if you’ve been thinking about doing yoga and lacking the motivation to actually roll out your mat at home or head to
        a class, you might be interested in this: yoga can actually help ease cramps, headache, anxiety, and other period-related symptoms. If you practice yoga for a long time, these
        benefits will be even more likely but even doing period yoga for 5 minutes can help even your most stubborn period pains disappear. Different poses have different benefits but
        we’ve rounded up 7 easy poses that will have you saying “ommmm” and “ahhhh”.</string>

    <string name="y11">Baddha Konasana (Bound Angle Pose) is a go-to pose for opening the hips and stretching the inner thigh muscles.This seemingly simple pose also strengthens
        your core and improves your posture.\n\n
        Also known as Cobbler’s Pose, this asana activates the muscles in your back as you lengthen and stretch through your spine.
        A strong and stable core is also key to this posture: “When you sit on the floor in Baddha Konasana, your core works to keep you from rounding the back and dropping the
            chest,” says yoga teacher Annie Carpenter, creator of SmartFLOW Yoga.\n\n
        While Bound Angle Pose may seem simple, if you stay in it for an extended period of time, your
        back muscles will likely tire, making it difficult to keep your chest upright, says Carpenter. Your hip, thigh, and hamstring muscles may also feel fatigued. If that happens, ease
        out of the pose.
            “Exploring your edges should not create pain,” she says. “It should help you move toward an amount of stretch or muscular effort that’s sustainable for you.”
    </string>

    <string name="y12">Bound Angle Pose can help you recover after running or other activities. It improves postural and body awareness and stretches your groins, inner thigh muscles
        (adductors), and front of your thighs (quadriceps).</string>

    <string name="y13">These cues will help protect your students from injury and help them have the best experience of the pose:\n\n
        1. If your back is tight or your posture needs attention,  sit with your back against a wall for support.\n
2. Never force your knees down. Instead, release the heads of the thigh bones toward the floor; your knees will follow. (Use blocks, folded blankets or pillows to support your knees.)\n
        3. If your knees are tender, move your feet further away from the groin.\n
            4. If you find it challenging to sit upright, place one or more folded blankets under your hips to lift your pelvis and spine.</string>

    <string name="y22">1. Stimulates abdominal organs like the ovaries and prostate gland, bladder, and kidneys\n
        2. Stimulates the heart and improves general circulation\n
        3. Stretches the inner thighs, groins, and knees\n
        4. Helps relieve the symptoms of stress, mild depression, menstruation and menopause
</string>

    <string name="y21">The Supta Baddha Konasana is one of the restorative yoga poses meant for sleeping and body correction. It instilled a sense of calm and relaxation in you and
        can be an answer to how to sleep easy or how to quickly fall asleep once you hit the sack.\n\n

The asana also helps you open up your hips and thighs, which in turn, makes other postures a walk in the park. The Supta Baddha Konasana is also referred to as the Reclined Goddess
        Pose, Bound Angle Pose Yoga or the Reclined Cobbler’s Pose.\n\n

The Bound Angle Yoga Pose should be performed in the morning, before breakfast. However, if mornings are not a suitable time for you, then evenings work too. One of the main Supta
        Baddha Konasana benefits is that performing the asana helps to sleep easily, but ensures there is a gap of three to five hours between the meal and the practice.</string>

    <string name="y23">To get all the Supta Baddha Konasana benefits it is important to perform the asana properly. Here are the steps to do this: \n\n

        1. To begin the Supta Baddha Konasana, sleep easily on the mat with your chest facing the ceiling.\n
2. Relax your shoulders and keep your spine straight. Make sure there is no strain on the neck and sleep easy. Also, double-check that the shoulders are not lifted off the mat.\n
3. Now gently bend the knees and bring the feet together. Make certain that your feet remain on the mat. Now slowly and gently bring your heels closer to the pelvic region. Your hands, during the asana, should lie next to the hips. Your palms should face the mat and should be pressed on it.\n
4. Now exhale and contract your abdomen muscles so that the tailbone moves closer to your pubic bone. There should be no pain in the lower back region as you stretch. If there is any pain, then immediately discontinue the bound angle pose yoga. \n
5. Perform them very slowly to bring stability to your spine and pelvis tilts. Quick movements can cause sprains. Hold this posture for about 20 seconds to get maximum benefits.\n
6. Inhale quickly, and then exhale slowly letting your knees to open, thus giving a good stretch in your pelvic region as well as inner thighs. Do not forcefully arch your spine, and always ensure that the shoulders relax and are not too close to the neck. Hold this pose for 30 seconds, breathing slow and soft.\n
7. Exhale and slowly come out of the pose. Be slower when coming out of any pose than you did while going into it. Your body is very tender when exiting a pose, and might get hurt if you are too quick. Also, before complete release, hold your knees together and slowly rock from one side to another for 10 seconds. This will help your body relax, sleep easy at night and get optimal benefits.\n
8. To deepen the pose, use your arms also. Raise your arms so that they are towards the ceiling. Broaden the shoulder blades across the back, inhale and stretch your arms over the head, floor and palms towards the ceiling. \n
            9. This pose can be followed by other poses like Malasana, Gomukhasan and Padmasana. </string>

    <string name="y32">Child’s Pose gently stretches the hips, thighs, and ankles. It relieves back and neck pain when done with head and torso supported. Balasana also calms the brain and helps
        relieve stress and fatigue.</string>

    <string name="y33">1. Sit on your heels, knees spread mat distance apart and bring your head towards the floor.\n
2. Your arms can be either stretched out to the front, by your side or hands underneath your forehead\n
3. Breathe into your lower back\n
4. Stay for anywhere between 30 seconds and several minutes in this resting pose\n
        5. To come out, exhale and roll up vertebra by vertebra, or come back to sitting with a straight spine.\n</string>
    <string name="y31">Bālāsana (Sanskrit: बालासन), Child Pose, or Child Resting Pose is a kneeling asana in modern yoga as exercise.
        Balasana is a counter asana for various asanas and is usually practiced before and after Sirsasana.</string>

    <string name="y41">Upavistha Konasana (Wide-Angled Seated Forward Bend) gives you the benefit of an intense stretch of the upper and lower body, as well as the calming effects of forward folds.
\n\nWhile this pose seems to be all about the leg stretch, give equal attention to lengthening your spine—creating long lines—and avoiding collapsing inward and sacrificing alignment. Tight hamstrings can interfere with this lengthening, says yoga teacher Natasha Rizopoulos.
\n\n“The hamstrings attach to the ischial tuberosities (sitting bones), which are the bony points that you can feel through the flesh of your buttocks,” she explains. “When the hamstrings are short, they pull the back of the pelvis down, creating what is known as a posterior tilt. This happens when you tuck your pelvis and round your lower back. ”
        Often times, the solution is to sit on a folded blanket. This elevates the hips, lessens the pull on the hamstrings and gives the spine more freedom to lengthen.</string>

    <string name="y42">Wide-Angled Seated Forward Bend lengthens the hamstrings and stretches the back, thighs and calves. It can increase mental calmness and decrease anxiety.</string>
    <string name="y43">1. Sit in Dandasana (Staff Pose), sitting directly on top of your sitting bones.\n
        2. Open your legs out to the sides as wide as you are able.  Flex your feet and point the toes up.\n
        3. Press through your big toe mounds and root down with your femurs so the quadriceps are also facing the ceiling.\n
        4. Inhale and lengthen your spine; exhale and hinge at your hips, walking your hands forward and bringing your torso to the floor between your legs.\n
        5. Keep the back straight and avoid curving the spine.\n
        6. To exit the pose, walk your hands back and return to Staff Pose.
</string>

    <string name="y51">Bharadvajasana (Bharadvaja’s Twist) is a seated pose that strengthens and stretches your spine, neck, and shoulders.
<br><br>It’s important to avoid doing this pose “head first”—in other words, tightening the muscles at the back of your neck, which can lead to headaches, upper back tension, and fatigue, says Denise Benitez, founder of Seattle Yoga Arts. To test your head position, lift your head upright and place the palm of one hand across the
        muscles at the back of your neck. If they’re hard and taut, bring your head back without lifting your chin.  You’ll feel the muscles at the back of your neck soften.</br></br></string>

    <string name="y52">Bharadvaja’s Twist improves postural and body awareness and can help stimulate proper digestion by facilitating movement through the digestive tract (peristalsis). This pose may help relieve constipation through the benefits of movement and stimulation of the lower abdominal area, and relieve bloating and gas. Bharadvaja’s Twist strengthens your core and particularly the muscles
        supporting your spine, stretches around your shoulders, your back muscles, front of your thighs (quadriceps), buttocks (glutes), and around your ankles.</string>
    <string name="y53">To enter this pose, start by sitting on your heels. To lessen the burden this posture places on your back and sacroiliac joints (they link your pelvis and lower spine), fold a blanket into quarters and position one corner of it so that it’s facing your right hip. Sit on the blanket with your right buttock, leaving your left buttock elevated off of the mat.
</string>

    <string name="y61">Although apparently a postural exercise, this technique has been spoken of as a Mudra (neuromuscular control). According to the authorities on Hatha yoga, this exercise of inverted balance has been formulated particularly with the object of bringing about inner harmony and union of the opposites, e.g. the bloodstreams (arterial and venous),
        the nerve impulses (afferent and efferent) and the positive and negative counterparts of bioenergy, with the aid of gravitation.</string>
    <string name="y62">Favourable changes in vasomotor ability (causing or relating to the constriction or dilatation of blood vessels) due to the increased interchange of blood in the upper part of the body,
        especially the thorax, the neck and the head the temporary replacement of the abdominal and pelvic viscera.</string>
    <string name="y63">1. Lie supine on the mat, feet together and hands resting beside the body. Keep the mind calm, body relaxed and take in a full breath.\n
        2. Exhaling, slowly raise the legs high up, perpendicular to the ground.\n
3. Raise the lower portion of the trunk by—pressing the hands under the hips and using the elbows as a fulcrum.\n
4. Keep the trunk in a slanting position, the legs upright and the back and the neck well-rested on the ground.\n
5. When this position is firmly secured, by careful manipulation, make an attempt to shift the hands slowly towards the waist, with the fingers extended to the back of the
        hip-bones and the thumbs pressed lightly on both sides of the navel (final position). Complete all the above steps in 4 seconds, while exhaling.\n
6. Maintain this pose as long as convenient, but not longer than two minutes. Breathe normally- slow, rhythmic and natural.\n
7. Return to starting position: Slowly bend the knees and then gently lower the hips towards the mat, supported by the hands in 4 seconds, while inhaling.\n
8. Release the hands from the back and assume the starting position.\n
        9. Take a few deep breaths and then rest a while, breath normally.</string>

    <string name="y71">Combining a forward fold, twist, and side body stretch all in one, Janu Sirsasana (Head-to-Knee Pose) can help calm your mind as well as stretch your body.
        Instead of rounding your back, lengthen your spine and bend from your hip crease. As you fold forward, close your eyes and cultivate a sense of inner peace.
        \n\nIllusions of grandeur can take hold when a desire to get as far as possible into an asana, or pose, takes you past your limits. These are as much asmita, or ego, as
            inability or meekness. In order to keep your ego in line with reality, approach any pose with humility and focus. Stay present, without trying to move too fast. Try to
            experience what you are feeling in your body without getting wrapped up in achieving a goal.
</string>
    <string name="y72">Head-to-Knee Pose improves posture and counteracts the effects of prolonged sitting. It can be helpful for recovery after sports and activities that include
        running. It stretches the back of your body, including your back muscles, and can help relieve low back tightness and low back pain. Also, it can bring calm to the mind and
        help with depression, anxiety, and fatigue.</string>
    <string name="y73">1. Begin in Dandasana (Staff Pose). Bend your right knee and place the sole of your right foot high on your left inner thigh.\n
2. Inhale and lengthen your spine; exhale and take your right hand to the outside of your left thigh and your left hand behind your left hip.\n
3. On an exhalation, bend at your hips and lean forward over your left leg.\n
4. Reach for your left foot. If it is available to you, clasp your left wrist with your right hand.\n
5. Inhale and reach your sternum forward; exhale and revolve your right ribs toward your left knee even more.\n
6. To exit the pose, inhale and lift your chest. Straighten your right leg, returning to Staff Pose.\n
        7. Repeat on the other side.</string>

</resources>